https://terstiege.de/index.php/privacy-policy/

The
following gives a simple overview of what happens to your personal
information when you visit our website. Personal information is any data
with which you could be personally identified. Detailed information on
the subject of data protection can be found in our privacy policy found
below.
Data collection on our website
Who is responsible for the data collection on this website?
The
data collected on this website are processed by the website operator.
The operator’s contact details can be found in the website’s required
legal notice.
How do we collect your data?
Data is collected automatically by our
IT systems when you visit the website. These data are primarily
technical data such as the browser and operating system you are using or
when you accessed the page. These data are collected automatically as
soon as you enter our website.
What do we use your data for?
Part
of the data is collected to ensure the proper functioning of the
website. Other data can be used to analyze how visitors use the site.
In no case are we going to share your data with third parties.
What rights do you have regarding your data?
You
always have the right to request information about your stored data,
its origin, its recipients, and the purpose of its collection at no
charge. You also have the right to request that it be corrected,
blocked, or deleted. You can contact us at any time using the address
given in the legal notice if you have further questions about the issue
of privacy and data protection. You may also, of course, file a
complaint with the competent regulatory authorities.
Analytics and third-party tools
When
visiting our website, statistical analyses may be made of your surfing
behavior. This happens primarily using cookies and analytics. The
analysis of your surfing behavior is usually anonymous, i.e. we will not
be able to identify you from this data. You can object to this analysis
or prevent it by not using certain tools. Detailed information can be
found in the following privacy policy.
You can object to this analysis. We will inform you below about how to exercise your options in this regard.
2. General information and mandatory information
Data protection
The
operators of this website take the protection of your personal data
very seriously. We treat your personal data as confidential and in
accordance with the statutory data protection regulations and this
privacy policy.
If you use this website, various pieces of
personal data will be collected. Personal information is any data with
which you could be personally identified. This privacy policy explains
what information we collect and what we use it for. It also explains how
and for what purpose this happens.
Please note that data
transmitted via the internet (e.g. via email communication) may be
subject to security breaches. Complete protection of your data from
third-party access is not possible.
Notice concerning the party responsible for this website
The party responsible for processing data on this website is:
Dipl.-Inform. Jochen TerstiegeIm Norden 445721 Haltern am SeeGermany
Email: info@terstiege.de
The
responsible party is the natural or legal person who alone or jointly
with others decides on the purposes and means of processing personal
data (names, email addresses, etc.).
Revocation of your consent to the processing of your data
Many
data processing operations are only possible with your express consent.
You may revoke your consent at any time with future effect. An informal
email making this request is sufficient. The data processed before we
receive your request may still be legally processed.
Right to file complaints with regulatory authorities
If
there has been a breach of data protection legislation, the person
affected may file a complaint with the competent regulatory authorities.
The competent regulatory authority for matters related to data
protection legislation is the data protection officer of the German
state in which our company is headquartered. A list of data protection
officers and their contact details can be found at the following link:
https://www.bfdi.bund.de/DE/Infothek/Anschriften_Links/anschriften_links-node.html.
Right to data portability
You
have the right to have data which we process based on your consent or
in fulfillment of a contract automatically delivered to yourself or to a
third party in a standard, machine-readable format. If you require the
direct transfer of data to another responsible party, this will only be
done to the extent technically feasible.
SSL or TLS encryption
This
site uses SSL or TLS encryption for security reasons and for the
protection of the transmission of confidential content, such as the
inquiries you send to us as the site operator. You can recognize an
encrypted connection in your browser’s address line when it changes from
“http://” to “https://” and the lock icon is displayed in your
browser’s address bar.
If SSL or TLS encryption is activated, the data you transfer to us cannot be read by third parties.
Information, blocking, deletion
As
permitted by law, you have the right to be provided at any time with
information free of charge about any of your personal data that is
stored as well as its origin, the recipient and the purpose for which it
has been processed. You also have the right to have this data
corrected, blocked or deleted. You can contact us at any time using the
address given in our legal notice if you have further questions on the
topic of personal data.
Opposition to promotional emails
We
hereby expressly prohibit the use of contact data published in the
context of website legal notice requirements with regard to sending
promotional and informational materials not expressly requested. The
website operator reserves the right to take specific legal action if
unsolicited advertising material, such as email spam, is received.
3. Data collection on our website
Cookies
Some
of our web pages use cookies. Cookies do not harm your computer and do
not contain any viruses. Cookies help make our website more
user-friendly, efficient, and secure. Cookies are small text files that
are stored on your computer and saved by your browser.
Most of
the cookies we use are so-called “session cookies.” They are
automatically deleted after your visit. Other cookies remain in your
device’s memory until you delete them. These cookies make it possible to
recognize your browser when you next visit the site.
You can
configure your browser to inform you about the use of cookies so that
you can decide on a case-by-case basis whether to accept or reject a
cookie. Alternatively, your browser can be configured to automatically
accept cookies under certain conditions or to always reject them, or to
automatically delete cookies when closing your browser. Disabling
cookies may limit the functionality of this website.
Cookies
which are necessary to allow electronic communications or to provide
certain functions you wish to use (such as the shopping cart) are stored
pursuant to Art. 6 paragraph 1, letter f of DSGVO. The website operator
has a legitimate interest in the storage of cookies to ensure an
optimized service provided free of technical errors. If other cookies
(such as those used to analyze your surfing behavior) are also stored,
they will be treated separately in this privacy policy.
Server log files
The
website provider automatically collects and stores information that
your browser automatically transmits to us in “server log files”. These
are:
Browser type and browser versionOperating system usedReferrer URLHost name of the accessing computerTime of the server requestIP address
These data will not be combined with data from other sources.
The
basis for data processing is Art. 6 (1) (f) DSGVO, which allows the
processing of data to fulfill a contract or for measures preliminary to a
contract.
4. Plugins and tools
Children under the age of 16
We
will not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from any
person under the age of 16. We encourage parents to instruct their
children to never give out personal information when online. Parents who
are concerned about the transfer of personal information from their
children may contact us via the website operator.
Google Web Fonts
For
uniform representation of fonts, this page uses web fonts provided by
Google. When you open a page, your browser loads the required web fonts
into your browser cache to display texts and fonts correctly.
For
this purpose your browser has to establish a direct connection to
Google servers. Google thus becomes aware that our web page was accessed
via your IP address. The use of Google Web fonts is done in the
interest of a uniform and attractive presentation of our website. This
constitutes a justified interest pursuant to Art. 6 (1) (f) DSGVO.
If your browser does not support web fonts, a standard font is used by your computer.
Further information about handling user data, can be found at https://developers.google.com/fonts/faq and in Google’s privacy policy at https://www.google.com/policies/privacy/.
